Guide to the Historic Photographs and Drawings Collection Photo.002
New York University Archives
- Series II: Glass Plates, 1883-1930
  - Students in Front of Gym, University Heights Campus, circa 1909-1910 (Box 2, Item 40)
  - Sports - Track, circa 1909-1910 (Box 2, Item 41)
  - Sports - Taking Photo of Event, circa 1909-1910 (Box 2, Item 42)
  - NYU - Map of Locations in New York City, circa 1909-1910 (Box 2, Item 43)
  - NYU - Map of Locations in New York City, circa 1909-1910 (Box 2, Item 44)
  - NYU - Map of Locations in New York City, circa 1909-1910 (Box 2, Item 45)
  - Organ at University Heights Campus, circa 1909-1910 (Box 2, Item 46)
  - Horse Drawn Carriage on Fifth Avenue, circa 1909-1910 (Box 2, Item 47)
  - New York Stock Exchange Exterior, circa 1909-1910 (Box 2, Item 48)
  - Glass plate negatives (slide box #1 and #2), 1883-1930 (Box Shared University Archives 019, Box Shared University Archives 020)